Guide to the English Language and Orientation Program, Summer Language Institute, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
English Language and Orientation Program, Summer Language Institute, Yale University, student records
1973-2002
RU 280
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
8
The records consist of student files of the Yale University Summer Language Institute, English Language and Orientation Program.
Yale Summer and Special Programs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 15-C (YRG 15-C), Student records from Yale summer and special programs. Organization: Arranged chronologically.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student files of the Yale University Summer Language Institute, English Language and Orientation Program.
Yale Summer and Special Programs; Yale University. Summer Language Institute
- Student records, 1973-1979; Accession 1983-A-117 (Box 1M)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - 1973 (Box 1)
  - 1974 (Box 1)
  - 1975 (Box 1)
  - 1976 (Box 1)
  - 1977 (Box 2)
  - 1978 (Box 2)
  - 1979 (Box 2)
- Student records, 1999; Accession 2004-A-090
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
- Student records, 2000; Accession 2005-A-073
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
- Student records, 2001; Accession 2006-A-121
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
- Student records, 2002; Accession 2006-A-122
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
- Student records, 2003- 2004; Accession 2007-A-047
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2080
  - 2003
    - Withdrawals
  - 2004
    - Withdrawals